Our society places a high value on physical beauty.
我们的社会非常看重外貌之美。
Americans spend an average of over $722 each year on their appearance.
美国人每年在外表上的花费平均超过722美元。
One in ten Americans has tried to look like a star.
每十个美国人中就有一个曾试图让自己看起来像明星。
There’s nothing wrong with trying to look our best, but excessive focus on physical appearance misses the soulful aspects of what it means to be beautiful.
努力让自己显得最好看并没有什么错，但过分关注外表，就会忽略美丽在心灵层面的种种内涵。
Trying to look like the magazine pictures can take us on a long ride away from what beauty is really about.
努力让自己看起来像杂志照片上那样，可能会让我们在偏离美之真谛的路上越走越远。
Many of us spend far too much time, energy, and money trying to polish an image of what we think will bring attention, love, and connection.
我们当中许多人花了实在太多的时间、精力和金钱，努力打磨一个我们认为能带来关注、爱和情感联结的形象。
In the process, we may fail to attend to ourselves in a way that would move us toward deeper intimacy, fulfillment, and meaning.
在这个过程中，我们可能会疏于以一种能引领我们走向更深的亲密关系、满足感和意义感的方式来关照自己。
It may sound trite, but beauty is only skin deep; it’s not what brings love toward us.
这话听起来或许是老生常谈，但美貌只是表面的；为我们带来爱的并不是它。
Just read about the latest Hollywood starlets whose seeming love turns into resentment and bitter court battles.
只要读一读好莱坞最新一批年轻女星的报道就知道了：她们表面上的爱情变成了怨恨和一场场激烈的官司。
Outer beauty can be as much of a curse as a blessing.
外在美可能是一种福分，但也同样可能是一种祸根。
We may develop a habit of being so focused on maintaining a perfect appearance that we never cultivate the inner qualities necessary to sustain and deepen intimacy and connection.
我们可能会养成一种习惯，过于专注于保持完美的外表，以至于始终没有培养起维系并加深亲密关系与情感联结所必需的内在品质。
As I describe in my book, The Authentic Heart, it is the courage to be authentic that connects us in a deeper way.
正如我在自己的书《真实之心》中所阐述的，正是做真实自我的勇气，让我们在更深的层面上彼此联结。
While our initial attraction may be based, in part, on physical chemistry, it is the meeting of our inner worlds that creates the lasting intimacy and spiritual connection for which we long.
虽然我们最初被对方吸引，可能在一定程度上是基于身体上的化学反应，但正是彼此内心世界的交汇，才会造就我们所渴望的持久亲密关系与心灵联结。
If we redirect our attention toward cultivating inner qualities, we might find a magnetic attraction that moves us from something superficial to something that connects us to our depths.
如果我们把注意力转向培养内在品质，或许会发现一种磁石般的吸引力，它让我们从流于表面的东西，转向能将我们与内心深处相联结的东西。
The path toward cultivating inner beauty is really simple.
培养内在美的道路真的很简单。
But what is simple is not always easy.
但简单的事并不总是容易做到。
Not everyone will see us and appreciate us as we take the courageous risk to allow ourselves to be seen as we really are.
当我们鼓起勇气冒险，允许自己以真实的面目示人时，并不是每个人都会看懂我们、欣赏我们。
But if they don’t, it is their loss, not ours.
但如果有人没能看懂我们、欣赏我们，那是他们的损失，不是我们的。
Eventually we’ll find those compatible souls who appreciate us as we are.
最终，我们会找到那些与我们心灵契合、欣赏我们本来样子的人。